1. randomEmail = custom.RandomData.generateRandomEmail()
5. randomUsername = custom.RandomData.generateRandomUsername()
9. openBrowser(URL)
13. maximizeWindow()
17. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
21. click(findTestObject("Registration/icon-acount"))
25. custom.BrowserHelper.closeFirefoxPopup()
29. click(findTestObject("Registration/btn-create-new-account"))
33. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-Email"), randomEmail)
37. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-account"), randomUsername)
41. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-Password"), "Laskar123456")
45. click(findTestObject("Registration/btn-sign-up"))
49. comment("Email used: " + randomEmail)
53. comment("Username used: " + randomUsername)
57. takeScreenshot()
61. closeBrowser()